本字幕 由 首发字幕组 原创翻译
本电影由 BT首发论坛 原创压制
www.BTshoufa.com
更多超清电影下载尽在 BT首发论坛
我向你们宣誓，
I swear to you,
在我们当中
every single mother and daughter,
被黑死病所杀害的每一对母女，每一对父子
father and son taken from us
都将可以复仇
by the Black Plague will be avenged.
这是他们的女巫王
It is their Witch Queen
给我们这片大陆带来诅咒的人
who brought this curse upon our lands.
她死后我们就能得到解放了
And in her death lies our salvation.
小心点，兄弟
Be warned, brothers.
她不会真正的死去
She will never truly perish
除非她的心脏停止跳动
until her heart beats its last.
我们不要害怕
Let fear be dead to us.
我们没有回头路了
There is no going back,
也没什么好回头的
for there is nothing to go back to.
这是什么，多兰？
What is it, Dolan?
我们周围充满了魔法
The Hexen are amongst us.
这个地方散发着死亡的气息
This place reeks of death.
大家要更注意点
Keep your wits about you.
别走散了
Stay close.
是她！
It's her!
是女巫王！
It's the Queen!
这是魔法
The magic.
不要靠近
Stay back!
用冷兵器和火!
By iron and fire!
救我们！
Help us!
-多兰！-女巫王！
- Dolan! - The Queen!
天父，
Heavenly Father,
保护我们免受恶魔的伤害。
protect us from these demons.
啊！
Ah!
保持阵型，兄弟！
Stay in formation, men!
爸爸！
Father!
爸爸，我好想你
Father, I missed you.
你不是真的
You're not real.
你不可能是
You can't be.
你们像老鼠一样繁殖
You breed like rats.
你们把石头叠起来
You put stone on top of stone
然后住在里面
and then live in your own filth.
你们是这个世界的入侵者
You are trespassers on our world.
这就是我制造瘟疫的原因
This is why I created the Plague.
这就是你们必须灭亡的原因
It's why every one of you must perish.
啊！
Ah!
用冷兵器
By iron
和火
and fire.
你爱的每个人都已经死了
Everyone you love is gone.
翻译：Tony  YAfish  Jolion Chan  莫夏  萱lo2e  fyemee  校对 ：真中
我在你眼里看到了
I've seen it in your eyes.
你希望死去
You wish for death.
今天我们俩都会死
Today we both die.
我用我的生命来诅咒你
I curse you with life.
永远看不到和平
To never know peace.
永远的孤独的活在这个世上
To walk the Earth alone for eternity.
你永远不会死
You will never die.
谢谢你
Thank you.
打扰一下，小姐？
Excuse me, miss?
先生，需要什么帮助？
Sir, how can I help you?
魔法
Magic.
嘿...
Hey...
看这个！
Watch it!
对不起，都是我的错
Sorry. Totally my fault.
打扰一下
Excuse me.
你是女巫猎人
You're the witch hunter.
是的
Yeah.
我什么都没做
I didn't do anything.
让我们看看这个
Let's see it.
看什么？
See what?
来吧
Come on.
女士们先生们，
Ladies and gentlemen,
飞机遇到突发情况...
the Captain has turned on...
很高兴你没弄湿它们
Be glad you didn't get them wet.
我找这些东西找了一段时间了
I've been looking for these for a while.
这是古时候留下来的
These are ancient runes.
它们能控制天气
They can manipulate weather.
下雨，刮风，寒冷，高温...
Rain, wind, cold, heat...
你就这样把它们包在一起扔在包里？
And you just jammed them together in your bag?
你知道在4万尺的高空
You know what you get when you mix a thunderstorm
雷暴和潮湿的寒冷空气混在一起会发生什么事吗？
with cool, moist air at 40,000 feet?
这是很简单的科学常识
It's simple science.
难以置信
Unbelievable.
作为一个女巫你竟然不知道你有什么样的能力
You witches have no idea the power you've got.
噢，我的天
Oh, my God.
你会把我抓到女巫委员会吗？
Are you gonna turn me over to the Witch Council?
不
No.
你要杀了我？
You're gonna kill me?
杀了你？
Kill you?
我阻止了你杀了你自己
I'm tryin' to stop you from killing yourself.
在纽约好好玩吧
Enjoy New York.
先生，“系好安全带”的信号灯在亮着
Sir, "Fasten seatbelts" signs are on.
你要坐回去
I need you to take a seat.
我叫考尔德
My name is Kaulder.
你要坐回你的位置，考尔德
I need you to get back to your seat, Kaulder.
我很高兴听到在塞夫鲁长大的人的声音
I'd love to hear about growing up in Sefrou.
你怎么知道？
How'd you know?
这几年都没有口音了
Haven't had an accent in years.
我在生命中遇到了很多人
I've met a lot of people in my life.
对此你很惊讶吧
You'd be amazed what you pick up.
女巫在我们之中秘密的生活
Witches live among us in secret.
他们的魔法在从远古的祖先中流传下来
Their magic passed down from an ancient race,
衰弱了，大半遗忘了，但仍然危险而强大
diluted, half-forgotten, but dangerously powerful.
经过几个世纪的冲突，签署了停战协议
After centuries of conflict, a truce was forged.
女巫允许正常生活并管理她们自己
Witches would be allowed to live
如果她们遵守一个严格的规定
and govern themselves if they followed
就是魔法绝对不能对人类使用
one strict rule, that magic never be used against humans.
停火协议是很容易破坏的
But a truce is a fragile thing.
有些人渴望
There are some who long for
恢复以前那样
the return of the old ways,
女巫王黑暗统治的日子
the dark days of the Witch Queen.
考尔德要处理的就是这些人
It is those whom Kaulder deals with.
八百多年来，他为十斧会干活
For 800 years, he has served The Axe and Cross.
我们一起看守和维护着和平
Together we have kept watch and kept the peace.
呃，对不起，多兰神父。他在开会
Uh, I'm sorry, Father Dolan. He's in a meeting.
噢
Oh.
会议结束了
The meeting has concluded.
我以一个特别的方式
I Serve The Axe and Cross
为十斧会服务
in a very different manner.
我是第36任多兰，并撰写了考尔德的历史
I am the 36th Dolan, and I write Kaulder's history.
我是他的左右手，他的教徒
I am his handler, his confessor,
但是，我喜欢认为我是他的朋友
and, I like to think, his friend.
你没有时间意识
You have no sense of time.
我当然有，只是和你的不太一样
Course I do. It's just different than yours.
我猜你的任务完成了？
I assume your mission was a success?
你安全的获得了天气符文
You recovered the weather runes without incident?
我给你的ipad怎么样了？
What happened to the iPad I gave you?
我转送给别人了
I re-gifted it.
我跟你都不适合用这个
We're not all as adaptable as you.
你知道纸张已经过时了
You know paper's the past.
记东西的时候仍然有用
It's also a useful object on which to record it.
你还记得路德维希的事吗？
Are you reminiscing about the Ludwig affair?
我现在心情不好
I'm in a sentimental mood.
啊
Ah.
关于我退休的事？
About my retirement?
这是你回来的原因
That's why you've come back.
我们合作得很好
We have had a good run.
我们取缔了一些讨厌的女巫会
We took out some nasty covens.
你真的准备好退休了？
You're really ready to call it quits?
只工作了50年
It's only been 50 years.
我终于习惯了你
I'm finally getting used to you.
噢，这就是你要说的吗？
Oh. Is that all it took?
我会想你的，孩子
I'll miss you, kid.
这是华特曼402
This is a Waterman 402.
我把你名字首字母刻上去了
I had your initials engraved on it.
它相当珍贵
It's very rare.
（把字母刻上去）可能会降低一点价值
Probably lowered the value quite a bit.
对我来说不是
Not to me.
如果你重新考虑，你仍然能拥有这支笔
You reconsider, you can still keep the pen.
我认为你会喜欢我的继承人的。
I think you'll like my successor.
我留给你一个更现代的帮手
I'm leaving you in more modern hands.
你的誓言怎么样？
What about the vow you took?
我发誓至死都会站在你身边
I vowed to face death at your side.
除非死去，不然我都会一直工作
Not to work until I keel over.
在你之前有35任多兰
Thirty-five Dolans have come before you.
只有你的建议
Here's to the only one
我才会听听
whose advice I ever listened to.
只是之后不采用
Only to ignore it.
但是我都有在听
But I always listen.
要是你也退休了呢？
What if you were retiring, too?
我是说，你会做什么
I mean, what would you do
如果下一个任务是你最后一个？
if your next mission was your last?
但是不会
But it won't be.
回答一下我的问题吧
Humor me.
我没抱怨
I have no complaints.
每天我醒来
Every day I wake up,
这个世界更宁静了些
the world sleeps a little easier.
考尔德，你的人生经历之丰
Kaulder, you have tasted more of life
比我能想象到的还要多
than I can ever imagine,
但是很长一段时间了你都没真正的活着
but it's been a long time since you really lived.
在我们短暂的存活的这段时间里
You're missing out on the best part
你错过了最好的一段
of our brief stay in this world.
就是你会跟人分享的这段时间
The part where you share it.
找一个值得信任的人
Find someone to trust.
我相信你
I trust you.
或许有人更合适
Perhaps someone a little more comely.
我知道，我没有活的
I know, I haven't lived
像你这么长而丰富
as long and rich a life as you,
但是我知道
but I do know that there is more to it
空姐除了要到处旅行之外
than a parade of stewardesses
还会演奏悦耳的月光奏鸣曲
marching to the dulcet tones of Moonlight Sonata.
现在你对于空姐
Now what in the world do you know
还知道些什么？
about stewardesses anyway?
我不是牧师出生
I wasn't born a priest.
我们干一些活先吧
Let's do some work.
我知道你认为这无聊
I know you think it's dull,
但是我们还是从头开始吧
but let's start at the beginning.
一句话都没说就走了
It goes without saying,
但你的工作真的超级棒
but you've served with great distinction.
如果可以的话，明天我见考尔夫的时候
If I may, when I meet Kaulder tomorrow,
我应该要做得很好才行，对吧？
I should play it cool, right?
在仪式结束前不喝咖啡
No coffee until after the ritual.
不要为你的风格担心
Don't worry about your style.
他怎样都会给你难堪的
He'll take the piss out of you anyway.
但是你会没事的
But you'll be fine.
这就是，呃，我担心考尔德的地方。
It's, uh, Kaulder that I worry about.
你担心考尔德？
You worry about Kaulder?
你知道十斧会的长者
Do you know how the elders
怎样评价他吗？
of The Axe and Cross refer to him?
他们说他是“武器”
They call him "The Weapon."
在我提交报告的时候
When I put in my reports,
他们都只想知道数字而已
all they want to know is numbers.
我拘留了多少个女巫
How many witches I've turned over for detention.
杀死了多少个违法的
How many slain for breaking the law.
这你能怪他们吗？他所做的都是很重要的
Can you blame them? What he does is so important.
是的，这是事实，但是他不仅仅是个武器
Yes, that's true, but he isn't just a weapon.
而我们是那些知道真相的人
And those of us who know the truth,
我们承担着责任
we bear responsibility.
不管发生什么事情，向我保证你要看护好他
Whatever happens, promise me you'll watch out for him.
当然，那是我的工作
Of course. That's my job.
出租车！
Taxi!
喂？
Hello?
考尔德？
Kaulder?
多兰36世在昨晚安详地去世了
Dolan the 36th passed away peacefully last night.
明天会举行葬礼
The ceremony will be tomorrow.
请节哀顺变
I'm sorry for your loss.
在你前面已经有36任多兰
Thirty-six have taken the name "Dolan" before you.
你是否能配的上第37任这个称号
Are you worthy of becoming the 37th?
我会证明给你看我配得上
I testify that I am.
你愿意承诺
Do you promise to serve
不顾一切的为我们的考尔德履行职责么？
our brother Kaulder in all things?
会像他了解他自己那样去了解他吗？
To know him only as he knows himself?
我愿意
I promise.
所以，你是新人咯
So you're the new guy.
我们之前其实见过
We've actually met before.
很久很久以前
A long time ago.
你看到那块基石吗？
You see that cornerstone?
我见人们把它立在那里的时候
I watched them lay it in
那里无非是块玉米地
when this was nothing more than a cornfield.
那才是很久很久以前
That was a long time ago.
我作为第37任多兰使者，愿意誓死效忠你
I pledge my life and loyalty to you as the 37th Dolan.
我发誓我会帮你履行你的使命...
I swear to help you carry out your duty to the Order...
当初在建造这个城市的时候
When they were building this city,
建筑工人在地下60英尺发现了
construction crews discovered
一个大墓地
a mass gravesite, 60 feet below ground,
里面都是那些被遗忘的奴隶
filled with thousands of forgotten slaves.
知道他们之后怎么做吗？
Know what they did?
不知道
No.
他们连夜把这些坑都埋了
Worked by night, filled the hole,
然后继续盖楼
and kept building.
到处都是恶魔的身影
There are shades of evil everywhere.
所以，我帮你办了
So, I'm sorting you out with
新的信用卡，新的护照和新的身份证
fresh credit cards, new passport, and a new identity.
习惯了用旧的了
Just gettin' used to the old one.
喔，那都过期了
Well, it's out of date.
现在全球资料库已经是一体化了，闭路电视
There are global databases now, CCTV's,
手机，位置追踪。世界一直在改变
smartphones and geotracking. The world is changing.
只仅仅在表面而已
Only on the surface.
没错，但是保持低调是很重要的。
Right. But it's important to keep a low profile.
嗯嗯
Mmm-hmm.
呃。。
Uh...
我想我们应该感激它不是红色的
I guess we should be thankful it's not red.
现在我们去哪？
May I ask where we're going?
我看过人们变老，退休，然后逝去
I've seen people get old, retire, and die.
但都发生在同一天却很少
Rarely on the same day.
他在桌子上被发现的
He was found at his desk.
我们在找什么？
What are we looking for?
你怎么知道附近什么时候有人施展魔法？
How do you know when there's magic in the vicinity?
施展女巫的魔法来自四种元素
A witch's magic comes from four elements,
火，水，土和空气
fire, water, earth and air.
运用正确的炼金术触发器
Applying the correct alchemical triggers
会暴露曾经施法的痕迹
will reveal its presence.
这里没有使用魔法
No magic here.
只是想确认一下
Just wanted to be sure.
如果窗口是关的
If the window hasn't been opened,
这些虫子是怎么进来的？
how did that get in here?
一只的话可以忽略
One means nothing.
两只的话可以说是巧合
Two, a coincidence.
三只就意味着麻烦事了
Three, trouble.
趴下！
Get down!
什么？
What?
他是被巫师杀死的
He was killed by witches.
在历史上十斧会的多兰
Never in the history of The Axe and Cross
从来没有被谋杀过
has a Dolan ever been murdered.
你想退出吗？
You wanna quit?
不想
No.
我想加人工
I want a raise.
这是在宣战
This is a declaration of war.
谁会做这些事？
Who could have done this?
施展这隐秘的魔法是为了
A concealment spell was placed
让所有东西都看起来很自然
to make everything look normal.
他们在找
They were searching for something,
一些不想让我们知道的东西
didn't want us to know.
元素魔法是中立的
Elemental magic is neutral.
从根本上既不是善的也不是恶的。
At its root it's neither good nor evil.
但是这不同
But this is different.
这些是黑魔法
This is dark magic.
凌驾于魔鬼
Beyond evil.
他们把他绑在椅子上
They tied him to the chair.
“死”
"Death."
这是咒语的一部分吗？
Is that part of the spell?
你在他死之前到过这里，对吗？
You were here last night before he died, right?
是啊
Yes.
让我看看你的手
Let me see your hands.
马上
Now.
我5岁的时候
I was five years old
女巫们把我们的屋子烧了
when witches set our house on fire.
我的父母被烧死
My parents died.
但是你走进大火里
But you walked through the flames,
用毯子把我卷起来
wrapped me in a blanket,
然后从二楼的窗口跳出去
and jumped out the second story window.
用身体垫着我着地
Your body broke the fall.
我已经告诉过你我们之前见过
I told you we'd met before.
如果你不记得，我从头细说
If you don't remember, I can refer you to the entry...
不用了，我记得
No. I remember.
你追捕那些女巫和给他们应有的惩罚
You hunted down the witches and brought them to justice.
我等了一辈子就是为了得到这个机会去帮助你
I've waited my entire life for the opportunity to help you.
那好，现在机会来了
Well, now's your chance.
你可以帮助我追捕干这事的女巫了
You can help me hunt the witches that did this.
我不应该要有一把枪或者铁棒之类的东西吗？
Shouldn't I have a gun or an iron mallet or something?
深呼吸下，集中精神。
Take a deep breath. Center yourself.
好，当然如此
Right. Of course.
因为抵抗魔法需要清醒的头脑
Because resisting enchantment requires a clear mind.
马克斯是14级的巫师
Now, Max is a 14th level warlock,
没有什么东西是你可以做的。可以放松一下。
there's nothing you can do. May as well relax.
免费试吃，神父？
Free sample, Father?
噢，谢谢
Oh. Thank you.
吃之前我都要再三考虑一下
I'd think twice about that.
只有1万块我不知道能不能做哦
I don't know that I can do $10,000.
你知道这个级别的魔法
You know the level of enchantment
其他人都这个价
they are getting from that.
我们的交易没问题，对吧？
Business is good, right?
好吧
Yeah.
噢，槽糕
Oh, crap.
到点关门了，马克斯
Shop's closed, Max.
考尔德，好久不见了
Kaulder. It has been too long.
售卖变思虫不是违法的
It is not illegal to sell mind-altering bugs.
当他们用在人类身上，这就是非法的
When they're used on humans, it is.
他们融入到蛋糕里面
They're mixing them in the cupcakes.
我没有留意
I hadn't noticed.
知道这个吗？
Notice this?
格里芬的天仙子，非常稀罕而且是禁止采摘的
Griffin's Henbane. Very rare and forbidden.
他们被用在通灵术上，黑魔法
This is used in necromancy. Dark magic.
你知道我从来都不做这类坏事
You know I do not deal in these kinds of bad things.
马克斯，你足够聪明不会走上这条路
Max, you're too smart to go down that road.
谁能想象我被骗了多少次
One can only imagine how many times I've been lied to.
超过历史上的任何人，实际上
More than anyone in history, actually.
得了吧，考尔德
Come on, Kaulder.
你必须明白，谁用上这种草药
You must understand, anyone who would use this herb
都是不怕你的。那才是让我害怕的！
is not afraid of you. And that scares me!
比我还让你害怕？
More than I scare you?
马克斯
Max.
来见我的那个人皮肤有一种气味
The man who came to see me has an odor on his skin.
一种像大蒜但是不是大蒜的气味
A whiff of garlic that was not garlic.
砒霜。还有么？
Arsenic. Anything else?
还有腐朽怨苹果。
And moldering crabapples.
多谢你，马克斯
Thank you, Max.
小心点
Be careful.
没有那习惯
Not in the habit.
不是你。是他。
Not you. Him.
所以这些对你有什么启发吗？
So, all that made sense to you?
这对你没有什么启发么？
It didn't to you?
没有
No.
砒霜在内战里是用来防腐的
Arsenic was used for embalming back in the Civil War.
杀了多兰的人曾经
Whoever killed Dolan
住在以前是葬礼堂的地方
is likely living in what was once a funeral parlor.
我们只需要找到有腐朽苹果树的地方就可以了
We just have to find one with a crabapple tree.
这是干嘛的？
What's that for?
乘车用的
A cab.
你不胜任接下来发生的事情
You're not qualified for what happens next.
噢
Oh.
好的。我会开收据的
Right. I'll get a receipt.
哇嗷
Whoa.
你妈妈没有教你
Didn't your mother ever teach you
不要吃树上的糖果么？
not to eat candy from trees?
回家吧，孩子
Go home, kid.
走开
Go away.
没事的
It's okay.
走开
- Get away from me. - Shh.
没事的
It's okay.
快给我走开
Get away from me now.
我不会伤害你的。走开！
- I'm not gonna hurt you. - Go away!
没事的
It's okay.
啊...
Ah...
噢，我靠
Oh, shit.
是你杀了多兰。为什么？
You killed Dolan. Why?
谁是那该死的多兰？啊？
Who the bloody hell's Dolan? Huh?
我这辈子从来没见过他！
I never met the man in my life!
你喜欢我的新笔吗？啊？
Do you like my new pen? Huh?
当我想像在委员会面前
When I imagined my first prosecution
第一次起诉
in front of the Council,
我是从来没想过
I never thought it would be
是一起针对我们的案件
for a crime against one of our own.
艾里克·雷曼斯奈
Ellic Lemasniel.
你好，神父。喔！
Hello, Father. Whoo!
你看起来很好人
You look like a good man,
很好吃的样子，你，我从来没。。。
tasty little thing, you. I never went...
请不要小看我
Please don't think less of me.
我迟点会认错的了
I'll confess it later.
巫师委员会会接收你的了
The Witch Council receives you,
十斧会第37任多兰使者。
37th Dolan of The Axe and Cross.
和平永存
The peace endures.
我现在把杀害第36任多兰使者的被告
I present the accused,
艾里克·雷曼斯奈
Ellic Lemasniel, for judgment,
带给你们审判
for the murder of Dolan the 36th.
我现在呈上在被告住所找到的证物
I present the evidence found in the accused's dwelling.
找到的？噢，拜托
Found? Oh, come on.
什么？你们看起来就像80年代那群糟糕的乐队
What? You look like a terrible band from the '80s.
看看你那头发！
Look at your hair!
他会得到应有的罪名的
He will be judged.
等等等等......
Blah, blah, blah.
你知道我的曾祖父的曾祖父
You know my great-grandfather's
曾经伺候过女王吗，啊？
grandfather served The Queen, huh?
女王
The Queen.
你们都是官僚主义的酒囊饭袋
You're a bureaucracy o' cowards
我不会承认
and I don't recognize the authority
在这个委员会上的权威
here in this council.
我也不会遵守你们的法律
Nor do I abide by your law.
法律服务来控制和维持魔法的
The laws serve to control and contain magic.
只有通过这个委员会的运作
It is only by the operations of this council
另一个战争才不会发生
that another war does not begin.
我没撒谎！我为我所做的感到自豪
I won't lie! I'm proud of what I done!
我杀害了你们的牧师
I murdered your priest!
我滴水滴干他，他就像一只蠢猪
I drip-dried him like he was a stuck pig!
我们的牧师，和我的朋友
Our priest, and my friend.
考尔德
Kaulder.
哦，糟糕，又是这家伙
Oh, shit. This guy again.
所以我们没有审讯也要审判他？
So we're to judge him without interrogation?
有人问过他，他给谁工作吗？
Has anyone asked him who he was workin' with?
没有三个五芒星卡
There's no Three of Pentacles card.
那就意味着他独自工作
That means he worked alone.
这些卡都是错的
The cards are wrong.
他施了一个形状转换的咒语
He cast a shape-shifting spell.
800年来我都我没见过那玩意儿
I haven't seen that crafted in 800 years.
自从女巫王的时代之后
Not since the time of the Witch Queen.
哈！女巫王死了很久了
Ha! The Witch Queen is long dead.
她的魔法是不可能重现的
That her magic could return is impossible.
- 不可能吗? - 是的
- Is it impossible? - It is.
- 你拥有权威... - 已经足够了
- You have the authority... - Enough!
把这个城市颠倒
To Turn this city inside out.
对于非法制造罪
For the crimes of illegal crafting...
找出他是和谁一起工作
Find who he's working with.
和人间的祭祀
And human sacrifice...
- 我为我所做的感到自豪 - 我们宣判
- And I'm proud o' what I done. - We sentence...
艾里克·雷曼斯奈
Ellic Lemasniel...
我为我所做的感到骄傲
I'm proud o' what I done.
- 监禁 - 我立场坚定
- To incarceration... - I took a stand!
在这房间基石的下方
In the bedrock beneath this chamber.
你是悲哀的...的反映
You are sad reflections of...
苏醒吧，哨兵
Arise, Sentinel,
把犯人带进监狱
and carry the condemned to prison.
你将永远不见天日
You'll never see daylight again.
不不！你现在可能会抓了我
No, no! You may hold me now,
但是你们将永远不会把我们全部抓住
but you'll never have us all!
那是什么
What is that?
嘿  孩子
Hey, kid.
你在干什么
What are you doing?
你好，神父
Hello, Father.
仍然跟我们在一起，老朋友
Still with us, old friend.
他还活着吗
He's alive?
仅仅活着
Barely.
他被诅咒了
He's been cursed.
怎么的？
How?
苍蝇座 马里
Musca Mali.
瘟疫横飞
Plague fly.
十三世纪的黑魔法
13th-century black magic.
它们是在女巫王的时候的树上被创造出的，对吗？
They were created in the tree of the Queen, correct?
是的
That's right.
为什么他们没有杀了他？
Why didn't they just murder him?
他们想审判他
They wanted to interrogate him.
当瘟疫驻扎在你身体里
When a Plague fly burrows inside of you,
就会破坏你的意识
it breaks your will.
无论凶手想知道什么
Whatever the killers wanted to know,
他都会告诉他们
he would have told them.
但问题依然存在，他们想知道什么？
But the question remains, what did they want to know?
他没有苏醒起来
He isn't getting up.
除非我们能打破诅咒
Not unless we could break the curse.
打破诅咒的唯一方法
And the only way to do that
就是杀了施法的女巫
is to kill the witch who cast it.
让艾里克为他卖命的那个
The one Ellic works for.
他顶多还有两天
Dolan's got two days, tops.
为了我，坚持住
Hang in there, for me.
死亡
"Death."
这是多兰留下的信息,而不是杀手的
It's a message from Dolan, not the killer.
回想起你的死亡
"Remember your death."
什么意思
What does it mean?
只有一个方式回想起我的死亡
There's only one way to remember my death...
魔法
Magic.
嘿，克洛伊
Hey, Chloe.
我这里还有一杯酒
I have one more drink here.
- 大家还好吗 -是的 ,我们都很好
- Are you guys okay? - Yeah, we're good.
我们会有一个很美好的晚上对吧，先生们？
Are we having a good night, gentlemen?
我们来谈谈恋爱吧，宝贝
Do a love shot with me, baby.
噢，不，我今晚不想谈恋爱
Oh, no. I'm not looking for love tonight.
- 大家都还好吗 -是的
- You guys okay? - Yep.
- 还想再要一个吗 - 好的
- Want another one? - All right.
哦，不，拜托！不，也不是你
Oh, no, come on! No, not you, too.
我听说你也不知道会发生什么事。好吗？
I heard that you can't tell before it happens. Okay?
他只是冰冷的站在那，然后...
He's just standing there all chilly calm, and then...
砰！他砍下你的头
Wham! He cuts your head off
把它挂在他的腰带上
and puts it in a sack on his belt.
拜托！这只是一个保姆告诉孩子们的故事
C'mon! That's just a story nannies tell children
让他们听话而已
so they behave.
克洛伊,你得离开了
Chloe, you need to leave.
米兰达  米兰达
Miranda. Miranda!
我们遵守法律，这里没有人类
We're up to code. There are no humans here.
好地方
Beautiful place.
谢谢你
Thank you.
你要多少钱
How much do you charge?
呃，那得看你买什么了
Well, that depends on what you're buying.
一个回忆
A memory.
500美金
Five hundred dollars.
成交
Deal.
我刚刚说的是“百”吗 ？我...
Did I just say "Hundred"? I...
不, 你知道吗? 我真实的意思是“五千”。
No, you know what? I actually meant "Five thousand."
5000元,这就是你的意思对吧？
Five thousand, is that what you meant?
对，就是五千
I did. I meant "Five thousand."
成交
Sold.
5万块
Fifty thousand.
我们可以开始了么？
Shall we start?
不行，你知道么？不行。
No. You know what? No.
我改主意了。我们...
I changed my mind. We're cl...
恐惧药剂
Fear potion.
在这个世界上还有什么是你害怕的？
Now, what in the world would you be afraid of?
公众演讲
Public speaking.
你知道我害怕什么？
You know what I'm afraid of?
说吧
Enlighten me.
我什么都不怕。这很无聊，真的。
Nothing. It's boring, really.
你看，我知道你们有法律
See now, I know that you have a code.
我还知道我并没有做错什么
And I also know that I haven't done anything wrong,
所以除非你拿把枪指在我的头上，不然就滚出去
so unless you're gonna put a gun to my head, get out.
你说的没错。我是有法律
You know, you're right. I do have a code.
但我并不会离开
But I'm also not leaving.
不管怎么说，你究竟要回忆剂干什么？
What do you want a memory potion for, anyway?
你是正在狩猎女巫吗？
Are you hunting a witch?
去救一个老朋友
To help an old friend.
给你一句忠告
But a word of warning to you.
如果你在你的记忆中受伤
If you get injured in your memory,
你也会在现实中受到同样的伤害
you get injured out here.
这意味着如果你在记忆中死去的话
Which means to say that if you die in there,
你真的会死...
you will also die...
我在哪都不会死
I can't die anywhere.
为了我的安全我必须跟你说清楚
I have to make a disclaimer for my insurance.
开启按钮啦
Bottoms up.
说“女巫猎人”
Say "Witch hunter."
女巫猎人
Witch hunter.
要乖乖的哦
Be nice.
回忆起你的死
"Remember your death."
你究竟想让我看到什么
What did you want me to see?
考尔德！
Kaulder!
考尔德。
Kaulder.
考尔德，醒醒。
Kaulder, wake up.
你好，女巫猎人
Well, hello, witch hunter.
我曾经有一次在回忆魔法中被叫醒
I was yanked out of a memory spell once.
几个小时之内我分不清东南西北
My mind was scrambled eggs for hours.
要知道，人们就不应该乱翻他们的记忆
You know, people shouldn't root around in their past.
一些东西最好被遗忘掉
Some things are best left forgotten.
呃...
Ah...
你诅咒了我的朋友
You cursed my friend.
你的朋友
Your friend,
他比大多数人只多坚持5分钟
he lasted about five minutes longer than most.
在酒吧打架的时候别拿太多的武器
Doesn't take much balls to get in a bar fight
你不会受伤
when you can't get hurt.
不幸的是，你的意志
Too bad your mind isn't as tough
并没有你其他部分强壮
as the rest of you.
不要再去酒吧了
No more bar.
别再使用记忆药剂了
No more memory potions for you.
把它吸进去
Breathe.
800年之后，你将要死了
After 800 years, you've run out of time.
死亡已经来临，巫师猎人！
Death is coming, witch hunter!
你就是他们说的怪物
You are the monster they say you are.
见鬼！这是我的全部！
Damn you! This place was all I had!
克洛伊
Chloe!
抓住我的手！
Grab my hand!
好美的景色
Nice view.
坚持住，孩子
Just hold on, kid.
我保证我会找到谁对你做了这些还会打破诅咒。
I promise I'll find who did this and break the curse.
考尔德！过来看一下！
Kaulder! Come see this!
我已经黑入了FBI网上数据库
I've got the FBI database online.
停下，上一条
Stop, go back one.
继续
Continuing.
不，不是他
No, not him.
停
Stop.
是他
That's him.
但是为什么他不想我去回忆我的死亡呢？
But why doesn't he want me to remember my death?
伯恩·巴尔塔萨·凯托拉
Born Baltasar Ketola.
现用名是彼列，芬兰国籍。
Goes by Belial. Finnish national.
艾里克就是为他工作的
He's the one Ellic was working for.
他就是那个诅咒多兰的人？
The one who cursed Dolan?
每一代人都会被赐予
Every generation has to be given
毁灭世界的机会
their chance to destroy the world.
但是大部分人不会像他一样，你知道
Yet most of us aren't like him, you know.
我们和你一样
We're the same as you.
你可能看起来像我们，但是你并不是
You may look like us, but you're not.
你的血液蕴含着魔法的力量
You've got magic in your blood.
能做非常坏的事的魔法
Magic that can do very bad things.
我们在你的酒吧被打断了
We were interrupted back in your bar.
- 对没错。 - 我必须要在尝试一次。
- Oh, yes. - I have to try again.
对了，我的酒吧！
Yes, my bar!
我所在乎的所有东西都被烧成了灰烬
Where everything I cared about burnt to the ground.
但是我并没有责怪你毁灭了
But I'm not blaming you for destroying
我的生活或什么东西
my life or anything.
我仅仅是在看着
I'm just making an observation.
看着你毁掉我的生活
An observation on how you destroyed my life.
我要走了
I'm leaving.
听着，我就像你一样不喜欢那样
Look, I don't like it any more than you do,
但是如果你能帮助我，我保证我会保证你安全
but if you help me, I promise to keep you safe.
我需要更多的斯诺登尼亚水
I'll need more Snowdonia hawkweed
来制作另一个记忆药剂
to mix another memory potion.
米兰达，那个为我工作的女孩
Miranda, the girl who works for me,
有一个非常好的储藏室
has a pretty good stash.
呃，我发个信息给他
Um, I'll text her.
谢谢
Thank you.
彼列的夹克上有红色的土壤
Belial had red soil on his jacket.
红土？
Red soil?
分析一下看我们能从中得到什么线索。
Analyze this and see what we get.
当然
Of course.
米兰达打过来的。
It's Miranda.
她是爱猫人
She's a cat person.
嗨！嗨，你好
Hey! Hey, there.
不，我还没死。
No, I'm not dead yet.
好了，当她到这里的时候
Right, so when she gets here,
不要做任何突然的动作，可以么？
don't make any sudden moves, okay?
不要有眼神接触
Don't make eye contact.
或者和她说话
Or talk.
哇
Whoa.
不好意思
Sorry.
这个就是了
This is it here.
不是，它还没有发芽
No, it hasn't sprouted yet.
你一共加入了多少个
How many witch hunter
巫师猎人讨论小组？
discussion groups are you a part of?
嗜杀、不朽的法西斯
"Genocidal immortal fascist..."
这就是你们女巫师眼中的我，是么？
So that's what you witches think of me, huh?
不管怎么说人们眼中的我们又是什么？
What is it that people know about us, anyway?
绿色的皮肤
That we have green skin
喜欢戴尖帽子，
and like to wear pointy hats,
然后我们是卑鄙的
and that we're mean
应该被绑在教堂的柱子上烧死？
and got burned at the stake in Salem?
教会错了
Salem was wrong,
那些女人是无辜的
and those women innocent.
但是如果那些女人真的是巫师呢？
But what if those women really were witches?
那是不是这样对待她们就是正确的呢？
Would it then have been okay?
我有时就在想如果我被发现有罪
See, I remember thinking if it was me found guilty,
没人会关心的
no one would care.
我会
I would.
水兰不见了。它不见了。
The hawkweed's gone. It's gone.
我意思是说有人把它拿走了。它不在这。
I mean, someone's taken it. It's not here.
考尔德？
Kaulder?
怎么了？
What?
- 什么？- 不
- What? - No.
米兰达。
Miranda.
米兰达！
Miranda!
你来迟了，巫师猎人。
You're too late, witch hunter.
她死的很痛苦，不停的尖叫
She died badly, screaming.
孤独
Alone.
你也会跟她一样
Just like you will.
你一定会抓到这个人的，是不是？
You're gonna get who did this, right?
我要搞定彼列
I'll handle Belial.
很好
Good.
我不知道还有什么地方可以找到我们需要的东西
I don't know where else to get the stuff that we need.
还有一个地方
There is one place.
但是那里用旧币，古老的魔法并且危险。
But it's old money, old magic, and dangerous.
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
考尔德？
Kaulder?
桑娅
Sonya.
丹妮现在真的很忙
Danique's been so busy,
我很惊讶她会你
I'm surprised that she agreed to see you.
我不认为她会喜欢
I don't think she would have liked
另一个选择
the alternative.
考尔德先生，你预定了我的夜晚
Mr. Kaulder, you've made my night.
请坐
Please have a seat.
你从哪里救得小朋友，一个旧货商店？
Where'd you rescue your little friend from, a thrift shop?
- 小朋友....- 噢...
- Little friend... - Oh...
告诉我吧，什么紧急情况？
So tell me, what is this emergency?
什么是你必须要回忆起来的？
What is it you just must remember?
他丢了他的车钥匙
He lost his car keys.
你要多少钱?
How much do I owe you?
一分钱不收。你只需跟我喝一杯就行了
Oh, nothing. You have a drink with me. That's my price.
你知道我来这里是干什么的
You know what I'm here for.
太多人把自己伪装成一个不真实的自己
So many of us pretend to be something that we're not.
但是你，你活了这么久
But you, you've lived.
穿越了整个历史
A man who's walked through history.
见过拿破仑，斯大林，
To have known Napoleon, Stalin,
希特勒
Hitler...
不需要怀旧他们。已经有够多的坏蛋了
No need to be nostalgic. We have enough evil now.
他们跟你很不一样
They're not so different than you.
他们用他们的力量来改变这个世界
They used their power to change the world.
而你做了之后并不能改变什么
You can't change what you've done.
考尔德！这棵植物有点古怪
Kaulder! There's something wrong with this plant.
你在这里
You're here.
考尔德...
Kaulder...
考尔德！考尔德！
Kaulder! Kaulder!
- 享受天堂吧。-考尔德！
- Enjoy paradise. - Kaulder!
考尔德，那是烟。不要
Kaulder, it's smoke. Don't...
看，爸爸。快看！
Look, Daddy. Look!
它们飞往南方过冬
They're flying south for the winter.
考尔德，听我说
Kaulder, listen to me.
你掉入陷阱了我需要你现在醒过来
You are in a trap and I need you to wake up.
你在这里肯定找不到任何答案
You're not gonna find any answers here.
你呆的时间越长越难以逃脱
The longer you wait, the harder it is to get out.
考尔德，考尔德
Kaulder. Kaulder.
我要你现在就醒过来，这些都不是真的
I need you to wake up. None of this is real.
考尔德，你掉进陷阱里面了！
Kaulder, you are in a trap!
快回来
Come back.
考尔德，如果你不能马上醒来
Kaulder, if you don't wake up right now,
我们都会死在这里！
we are both going to die!
给我醒醒！
Wake up!
克洛伊....
Chloe...
这不是真的
This isn't real.
考尔德！快醒过来！
Kaulder! Wake up!
把车停到小巷子里
Pull the car into the alley
把他丢到后备箱
and throw him in the trunk.
我们会将会被载入史册
We're going down in history
作为打倒巫师猎人的人
as the ones who beat the witch hunter.
搞定他
Come on.
出去
Get out.
墓地的泥土
Burial dirt.
用这个来施展黑魔法是厉害的了
Nothing more powerful for dark magic.
彼列要用这个干啥？
What does Belial want with it?
谁？
Who?
“回忆起我的死亡”
"Remember my death."
他不想让我看的是什么
What is it that he doesn't want me to see?
停下！求你了
Stop! Please.
彼列什么都没和我说
Belial didn't tell me anything.
我帮他弄到了泥土
I helped him get the dirt.
我只是给自己留了一点点
I just took a little bit for myself.
他有特别多
He has tons of it.
请饶了我？
Please?
谢谢你的酒
Thanks for the drink.
你是种族的叛徒
You are a traitor to your kind!
你知道我最喜欢旧货店里的什么吗？
You know what I like about thrift shops?
旧货店里什么都是旧的
Everything in them is old.
哦!
Oh!
婊子！
Bitch.
所以先在你知道了
So now you know.
你是一个梦行者。
You're a dream-walker.
每个人都知道梦行是黑色天赋
Everyone knows that dream-walking is a black gift.
我一辈子都在躲着这个天赋
I've spent my entire life trying to hide from it.
你知道我会发现你的秘密，但是你不在乎
You knew I would discover your secret, and you didn't care.
你还是把我从陷阱中拉出来
You still pulled me out of that trap.
胆儿够大的
It was a very brave thing to do.
给你看点东西，过来。
Let me show you something. Come on.
晚安，马克思！
Good night, Max!
你是我们种族的耻辱
You are a disgrace to our kind.
彼列，我毫无选择
Belial, I had no choice.
考尔德威胁要徒手揍死我
Kaulder threatened to beat me to death with his bare hands.
叛徒，我们帮你弄了个计划
We have plans for you, traitor.
彼列，你要谅解我
You must understand, Belial.
在阴暗里永劫不覆吧
Enjoy the shadows.
这就是巫师的历史。你们的历史
This is the history of witches. Your history.
这是你
That's you.
嗯
Yeah.
至少，他们没把你眼睛搞错。
Least they got your eyes right.
这些是梦行者
These are the dream-walkers.
巫师皇后的致命杀手
The Witch Queen's deadliest assassins.
他们习惯于跳进你的思维中
Somehow they used to jump into your mind
找出你最珍贵的记忆
and pry out your most precious memories.
然后再把它们扭曲成噩梦
And then they'd twist 'em into your worst nightmares.
你这是给我上历史课呢?
What, you're giving a history lesson here
还是在吓我？
or you're just trying to scare me?
梦行者的一些事情别人并不知晓
There's something no one knows about dream-walkers.
他们并不需要记忆药水
They don't need memory potions.
他们的力量是与生俱来的
That power lies within them.
我有些记忆被我深深掩埋了
I have something buried deep in my mind
但那些是我必须要回忆起的
that I must remember.
你是唯一可以帮助我的人
And you're the only one that can help me.
不，我不行
No, I can't.
克洛伊..
Chloe...
不，我不行
No, I can't.
你知道，我还有个小弟弟
You know, I have a younger brother,
并且
and, uh,
他总能把我惹毛
he had this knack for just pissing me off.
有一天他做得太过了
And one day he pushed it too far,
于是我就进入他的脑子里
and I somehow entered his mind.
我伤害了他，我不是故意的
I hurt him. I didn't mean to,
但我伤害他很深
but I hurt him badly.
所以我逃跑了
So I ran away.
你老婆和女儿的名字是什么？
What were their names, your wife and daughter?
海伦娜
Helena.
伊丽莎白
Elizabeth.
我很久没把他们的名字说出来了
I haven't said their names out loud in a long time.
考尔德，即使我想帮你
Kaulder, even if I wanted to help you,
我也不知道怎么开始
I wouldn't know where to begin.
想一个和我俩都相关的词
Think of a word that you associate with me.
可以是任何事
Could be anything.
清空你的大脑
Empty everything else out of your head.
把注意力集中在那个词
And just focus on that one word.
一个词
One word.
你告诉我这个词，我也把注意力集中在这个词
If you tell me the word, I'll focus on it, too.
有时有用
Sometimes that helps.
哪个词？
What's the word?
孤独
Alone.
握着我的手
Take my hand.
这边！
This way, men!
多兰大哥，看
Brother Dolan, look.
考尔德
Kaulder.
那是什么？多兰？
What is that? Dolan?
小心走过去
Tread with care.
他做到了
He did it.
他了结了女巫王
So ends the Queen.
以神父之名...
In the name of the Father...
他被控制了！
He's possessed!
考尔德还活着
Kaulder is alive.
我们的噩梦奇迹般地结束了
Our nightmare ends with a miracle.
救救他
Help him.
是她的心
It's her heart.
我们摧毁了它，也就摧毁了她
When we destroy it, we destroy her.
多兰大哥，了结了它
End it, Brother Dolan.
多兰，杀了她！
Destroy her, Dolan!
不！
No!
你把它留下了
You kept it.
结束了，女巫王死了
It's over. The Witch Queen is dead.
从一开始他们就背叛了你
They betrayed you from the start.
那就是他们要折磨你朋友的原因
That's why they tortured your friend.
因为他知道那颗心脏在哪里
Because he knew where the heart was.
他们想要将女巫王复活
They're gonna bring back the Queen.
过去800年间
For eight hundred years,
我们都在等待她的归来
we've waited for her return.
你应该感到荣耀，叛徒
You should be honored, traitor.
你将会为了我们的事业而被献祭
You will be sacrificed for our cause.
考尔德，我知道彼列在哪买的那些黑土
Kaulder, I know where Belial brought all that dirt.
他租的那台卡车装了标准的GPS定位器。
The truck he rented had a standard GPS locator...
你撒谎！
You lied to me!
你保存了她的心脏。“回忆起你的死”。
You saved her heart. "Remember your death."
不是你想的那样
It's not what you think.
你一直都知道那意味着什么，你却什么都没说
You knew what it meant all along, and you said nothing.
因为我不想一上任就要
Because I wasn't going to be responsible
为十斧会的灭亡负责...
for the dissolution of The Axe and Cross on my very first...
他们正召回女巫王
They're bringing back the Queen.
你都干了些什么！
You don't know what you've done.
我发誓要保守秘密
I swore an oath to keep it secret.
数百年来世界没有因为这个谎言而毁灭
This lie has kept Apocalypse at bay for hundreds of years.
我们曾担心如果女巫王的心被毁灭的话
We were afraid if the Queen's heart was destroyed,
你将会失去你的永生能力，甚至死掉
you'd lose your immortality. Or die.
那不是你要做的选择
That wasn't your choice to make!
那是那个老人的想法
That's what the old man thought.
他被袭击的那晚
The night he was attacked,
我以为他会毁掉它的
I think he was going to destroy it.
为了你
For you.
为了解放你
To set you free.
至少十斧会仍有他们的武器
At least The Axe and Cross still has their weapon.
你将会侍奉女王
You will serve the Queen...
请不要这样！
No, please.
由不得你
Like it or not.
啊！
Ah!
去我的公寓，你在那很安全。
Go to my apartment. You'll be safe there.
不，说好了我们要在一起的
No, the deal was that we stick together.
我要自己去，如果我连自己人都不能相信
I'm going alone. If I can't trust
我又怎么能相信你呢？
my own people, how the hell can I trust you?
这不像你
This isn't who you are.
这才是全部的我
It's all I am.
用冷兵器刺她
Pierce her with iron.
用火烧她
Scour her by fire.
就可以让她真正的死去
Bring her endless death.
我一直在想你，考尔德
I've missed you, Kaulder.
这是你不会明白的
Here's what you don't understand.
你们种族都不会明白的
What your kind never understood.
我已经仁至义尽了
I've shown mercy.
我本来可以杀光你们每一个人的
I could have killed every last one of you.
我已经统计好了
I've done the math.
而且我有的是时间
I've had the time.
你现在不同了，如此自信
You're different now. So confident.
也许你不应该让我永生
Maybe you shouldn't have made me immortal.
考尔德，我来帮忙了。
Kaulder, I came to help.
克洛伊，我告诉过你不要...
Chloe. I told you not to...
永生的权利从来都不属于你，它是我的
Immortality was never yours. It was mine.
你只是帮我保管而已
You just carried it for me.
直到现在
Until now.
我又重生了
I am reborn.
啊！
Ah!
你们这个种族...
Your race
总是心存恐惧
has always been frightened.
隐藏在深处
Hiding in caves.
蜷缩在篝火旁
Huddling around fire.
终于
Finally.
嘿，孩子。我还担心来晚了
Hey, kid. I was afraid I was too late.
我希望自己看起来不像你这样难看
I hope I don't look as rough as you do.
好吧
Okay.
我杀了那个诅咒你的家伙
I killed the one who cursed you.
过来
Here.
喝了这杯
Drink this.
谢谢
Thank you.
女巫王复活了
The Witch Queen has returned.
我曾以为我的永生...
I thought my immortality
是她用来惩罚我的
was the way that she punished me.
但她只是利用我来为她自己保管这种能力
But she just used me to save it for herself.
恐怕我得承担一些责任
I'm afraid I bear some responsibility.
这样想真是过分狂妄了
It was hubris to think
我们的秘密不会被敌人发现
that our secret wouldn't be discovered by the enemy.
我已经预见接下来会发生什么了
I've seen what comes next.
死亡
Death.
女巫王将会散播更多的诅咒
The Witch Queen will cast another plague curse.
拥有那种力量的女巫们没有被摧毁吗？
Haven't covens with that kind of power been destroyed?
我们不再消灭女巫了
We don't destroy witches anymore.
我们监禁她们
We incarcerate them.
我们抓住了所有最有力量的女巫
We took all the most powerful witches
她们曾横行世上
that ever walked the Earth
把她们关进了一个地方
and put 'em in one place.
女巫监狱
The witch prison.
她们仍在等待着，等待着被释放...
And they've been waiting, waiting to be released.
等待着复仇
Waiting to exact revenge.
我们创造了完美的女巫聚会
We created the perfect coven.
现在我回到了原点
Now I'm right back where I started.
你打败过她
You defeated her once.
你还会再次击败她
You can defeat her again.
考尔德
Kaulder,
你得走了
you must go.
你必须战斗
You have to fight.
考尔德
Kaulder.
我从未给它起过名字
I never had a name for it.
但我的敌人都叫它“屠巫剑”
But my enemies came to call it "Hexenbane."
女巫杀手
Witch Slayer.
我也来了
I'm coming, too.
我们约定的前提是能保证你的安全
Our agreement depended on me keeping you safe.
不，我们约定的是如果我帮助了你
No, our agreement was that if I helped you,
你就得保证我的安全
you'd keep me safe.
如果我现在受伤了，我就一直伤着
If I get hurt now, I stay hurt.
它会好吗？
Where would that leave you?
你知道，我不管！
You know, I don't care!
谁说了一个女巫不能猎杀其他女巫？
Who says that a witch can't hunt witches?
克洛伊...
Chloe.
克劳德...
Kaulder.
这是什么？
What is this?
这是灾难树。她在这儿。
It's a plague tree. She's here.
当咒语许下
When the spell is done,
铺天盖地的苍蝇将会被释放
the fly swarm will be released.
我们没有太多时间了
We haven't much time.
跟紧些
Stay close.
考尔德，犯人去哪了？
Kaulder, where are the prisoners?
天哪！
My God!
每一个我曾抓到过的女巫
Every witch I ever caught.
女巫正用她们的力量来释放诅咒
The Queen's using their power to release the plague.
她是怎么做到的？
How?
用圣歌
The chant.
没有女巫拥有如此强大的力量，
No witch would be strong enough
能够单独施咒。
to cast this spell alone.
但女巫王...
But the Witch Queen's
却可以将她们的思想像锁链一样连起来
linking their minds like a chain.
那我们要怎样阻止她们呢？
So how do we stop them?
每条锁链都有一个薄弱的环节
Every chain has a weak link.
- 这个我来吧.-不！
- I'll do the honors. - No.
我们不是要毁掉他的身体
It's not his body we need to destroy.
而是他的意识
It's his mind.
但如果他死在他的梦里
But if he dies in his dreams,
诅咒将会停止
the plague will be stopped.
我希望还有别的办法
I wish there was another way.
你会一直在这等着我回来，对吗？
You'll still be here when I get back, right?
你要单独去对付女巫王，是吗？
You're taking on the Queen alone, aren't you?
必须有个了结
It has to end.
嘿！
Hey.
去那儿小心
Be careful in there.
那你会担心我吗？
So are you worried about me then?
呃，我已经习惯你了
Well, I've gotten used to you.
祝你猎杀成功
Good hunting.
你也是
You, too.
守卫
The Sentinel.
它不会停止 除非这个囚犯
And it won't stop until this prisoner
被押他的牢房
is put back in his cell.
它是冲着艾里克来的
It's coming for Ellic.
考尔德
Kaulder?
如果她有在那边受到伤害的任何迹象
If there's any sign she's getting hurt in there,
你必须叫醒她
you have to wake her up.
并且向我保证带她走得
And promise me you'll get her as far away
越远越好
from here as you can.
必须的
Of course.
圣歌停下来了
The chanting stopped.
她做到了
She did it.
梦行者向你展示了过去
A dream-walker shows your past.
只有我能昭示未来
Only I can show the future.
你们将会失败，而人类将会堕落
You will fail, and humanity will fall.
我把世界恢复成原来那样了
I've taken this world back.
还没有
Not yet.
感觉到了吗？
Can you feel it?
你的凡身
Your mortality?
你的生命正在流逝
Your life ebbing away?
父亲
Father!
考尔德
Kaulder.
你是我们这个世界的入侵者
You are trespassers on our world.
父亲
Father!
我已经透过你的眼睛看到了
I've seen it in your eyes.
你盼望死亡
You wish for death.
你明白永生的好处吗？
You know the benefit of eternal life?
我应该杀死你两次的
I get to kill you twice.
快住手！
Stop!
考尔德
Kaulder!
那么...
Now...
—克洛伊...—对不起
- Chloe... - I'm sorry.
释放我的女王
Release my Queen.
当我还是个孩子的时候，你从那些女巫手中将我救出
Those witches you rescued me from when I was a kid...
她们并没有杀害我的父母，他们就是我的父母
They didn't kill my parents. They were my parents.
但不幸的是，我天生没有法力。
But sadly, I was born without magic.
你是个女巫
You're a witch.
是的
Yep.
—不！不！—快回到这儿！
- No! No! - Get back here!
快离开他！放开他！
Get away from him! Let go!
梦行者
Dream-walker.
看看你自己
Look at you,
你那丑陋的女巫脸
you ugly bitch of a morning.
你背叛了那些
You turned against those
你应该要保护的人们
you were charged with protecting.
是的，女王
Yes, my Queen.
让我完整吧，帮我到达我的宿命。
Make me whole. Help me reach my destiny.
赐予我魔力吧
Grant me the gift of magic.
沙土不会变成金子
Clay cannot be turned to gold.
没有法力，你只是个凡人。
Without magic, you're just a human.
父亲？
Father?
亲爱的
My love.
你必须起床了
You must get up.
父亲，你得起床了
Father, you need to get up.
去救他们
Save them.
去吧！亲爱的，去战斗吧！
Go, my love. Fight.
你还在垂死挣扎
You cling to your pathetic life.
为了什么呢？
And for what reason?
最亲近的人背叛了你
Those closest to you betray you,
而那些你宣誓要保护的对象甚至都不知道你的名字
and those you claim to protect don't even know your name.
用钢铁
By iron
和烈火
and fire!
试着用ipad来做吧
Try doing that with an iPad.
考尔德
Kaulder!
Kaulder?
考尔德
只要心脏还在跳动
As long as the Hexen heart beats,
她就不会真的死去
she's never truly dead.
不，你不要！你会死的
No, you can't! You'll die.
我已经准备好面对现实了
I'm ready to face that reality.
不！一定有别的办法
No! There must be another way.
听我说
Listen to me.
当我被拉入黑暗中时
When I was pulled into the shadows,
我看见了比她更可怕的东西
I saw that there were things much worse than her.
在黑暗中，静静等候
In the darkness. Waiting.
等待什么？
Waiting for what?
一个没有你的世界
The world without you.
我们仍需要你
We still need you.
我需要你
I need you.
十斧会背叛了我
The Axe and Cross betrayed me.
我不再相信任何人
I can't trust anyone.
你可以相信我
You can trust me.
我已经在这条路上走了800年
800 years I've been on this road.
一直在狩猎
Always hunting.
一直是...孑然一人
- Always... - Alone.
不会再是了
You wouldn't be.
另外
Besides,
你还欠我5万块
you still owe me fifty thousand dollars.
5千块
Five thousand.
好吧，这么说我们是在砍价了，是吗？
Oh. So we're negotiating, then?
十斧会将很头疼
The Axe and Cross would be bothered that
她们不再拥有
they're no longer in possession
女巫王的心脏
of the Queen's heart.
我不再帮十斧会工作了
I don't serve The Axe and Cross anymore.
这次我为自己而做的
This time I do it for me.
好吧，这是关于时间
Well, it's about time.
我过去总认为
You know, I used to think
宇宙循环往复、周而复始
the universe ran in endless circles,
总在重复着自身，永远可以预测
always repeating itself, always predictable.
那现在呢
And now?
我不知道接下来会发生什么
I don't know what happens next.
你知道我们凡人怎么称它吗
Do you know what we mortals call that?
生活
Living.
你知道
You know,
我仍需要你
I still need you.
那么
Well, then
我为你效劳
I'm at your service.
得了吧，你不会再年轻了
Come on. You're not getting any younger.
你是准备走，还是怎样
So you ready to go, or what?
我来开车
I'm driving.
好吧
Okay.
谢谢观赏
本电影由 BT首发论坛 原创压制
www.BTshoufa.com